Search carefully.
Don't miss a single corner.
Something feels wrong.
They must have alerted the enemy,
and let Qian Yanqing escape.
Could it be that the three of them
distracted us on purpose?
What are you talking about?
Wrap it up.
Why does this sachet look familiar?
Li Chengrui didn't catch Qian Yanqing
and went back to the police station.
How are we going to investigate next?
If it's an organized trafficking of women,
we must find
the criminals' lair.
I'm good at disguises.
I'll go.
No.
Senior Sister,
let me go.
I'm about the same age as Lingling.
I should be their target.
I'll be the bait
and infiltrate the criminal ring.
No, it's too dangerous.
Yeah.
I have other plans for you two.
Shi'an.
You guys follow me then.
I'll leave clues for you.
Siyao.
Didn't you say I suspected you?
Now,
I'm trusting you with my life.
Okay.
Officer,
please save my daughter.
She's only sixteen.
Your police department is too inefficient.
It's been three days since we reported it.
Why haven't you handled it yet?
If you don't give us an explanation today,
we're not leaving.
We need time to investigate.
Seriously, why are you guys like this?
Yes, yes.
It's already being handled.
This is bad.
What's wrong?
More and more girls are going missing.
The parents who reported it have surrounded the police station.
It's a complete mess outside.
Then go handle it quickly.
What's the use of complaining to me?
In the past, in situations like this,
Inspector Jiang would always step in.
I...
You are just a piece of trash.
L-Lord Huo.
Lord Huo.
Why are you here?
You should have let me know.
I would have picked you up.
My Huo residence is quite lively today.
So many citizens
want me to seek justice for them.
Look at the streets now.
People are already petitioning.
Li Chengrui,
are you completely useless?
Do I need to call Mayor Zeng
and have you replaced?
No, no, no.
It's already being resolved.
Hurry up and get Detective Jiang back.
Um,
Officer Huo.
Please ask Detective Jiang to make an appearance.
Detective Jiang is missing.
I even think
you did this, Superintendent Li.
How is that possible?
No.
Detective Jiang and I
just have different ideas about handling cases.
How could I harm her?
Yao Qiang, don't just stand there.
Go, go, go.
Hurry up and find her.
Go quickly.
Right away.
My lady.
Did I do okay just now?
Li Chengrui's words
are credible.
In my opinion,
this matter should have nothing to do with him.
Think about it.
If Jiang Siyao solves the case,
Li Chengrui will just wait to take the credit.
So he needs Jiang Siyao.
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
I think Jiang Siyao
has already entered the tiger's den.
What are you guys doing?
You...
Why are you wearing clothes like this?
This is a school uniform.
The school makes us wear it.
Then you...
Why do you go to a Westerner's school?
Schools...
Schools are of course for learning knowledge.
Nonsense!
Do you know
that all Western things
are foreign religions
used to bewitch people's minds
and corrupt human bodies?
Using Westerners' things
and learning Westerners' knowledge,
sooner or later you will
become slaves to Westerners,
and after death you will surely fall into the Avici Hell.
How is that possible?
Schools are for increasing knowledge
and enlightening the people.
Worshipping foreign things,
straying from the righteous path.
Punish!
What are you doing?
Why are you hitting me?
Help! Help!
Only Lord Jumang can save you
and save the world.
May you soon hear the true voice
and wash away your sins.
New disciple,
quickly kneel and worship Lord Jumang.
I won't kneel.
Stubborn and foolish.
I absolutely will not kneel.
Blaspheming the Lord.
Come, get up.
Since you have worshipped the Lord,
you are now an official disciple of the Jingxiang Society.
Your Dharma name
will be Jingxin.
Jingzhi,
she will cultivate with you from now on.
Yes, Venerable.
Senior Sister,
how long have you been here?
How many people are in here?
From now on,
you will sleep here.
No, I...
I'm sleeping here?
All these clothes of yours,
we will throw them away.
But...
Here,
you can only wear this.
Just these ragged clothes?
You...
From now on,
no foreign items are allowed here.
Otherwise, you will be punished.
Got it?
Let's go.
Reporting to Superintendent Li.
I spent the whole day
checking people entering and leaving the city.
I didn't find anything suspicious.
I checked all the streets
and brothels in the city,
but found no clues about Detective Jiang.
Did you go to investigate a case
or visit brothels?
How could the kidnappers
hide someone in such an obvious place?
You mean...
Hurry up and find him!
Yes, sir.
Why didn't you tell me you were here?
You're finally back.
Any news?
I sent many people to look for him,
but they couldn't find him.
So many people and still nothing?
Eliminate all foreign influence.
Restore our traditions
and keep our hearts pure.
Start with me.
Please,
help me find my daughter, Detective Jiang.
Lingling.
Every meal is hard-earned.
They are all bestowed by the Heavenly Lord.
Do not waste them.
Let's eat.
Lingling.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here to save you.
How is it?
Did you find her?
Young Master.
As you instructed,
we used all our connections
to look for places where girls gather.
Currently,
there are no clues.
What about checking the carriages entering and leaving the city?
There is a village that is quite strange.
It was originally a poor village,
but recently carriages have been coming and going frequently.
I checked,
and there are no new industries.
That's all the information I have.
Okay.
I'll go check it out.
You go look for her.
Time waits for no one.
The later we find Siyao, the more danger she will be in.
By the way,
here is what you asked me to bring.
Let's go.
Who is this person?
A distant relative of mine.
He asked me to get him a residence permit.
I have already sent the Huo family
to expand the search area.
They've gone outside the city.
Do you have any news?
Baxian Village.
Lingling,
do you know where this is?
How many people are here?
There is one Venerable,
three Masters,
and about a dozen Protectors.
The rest
are female disciples like us,
about twenty or thirty people.
The Venerable,
is he the boss here?
There seems to be a Grandmaster as well.
I just got here and haven't seen him yet.
Jingxin, Jingyan,
you two have violated the rules.
No lunch for you today.
Moxa floss.